>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我把这个给一个我想做的案件
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let me bring this
down to a case that I wanna make,
这件案子比我们的案子更直接
and this is much more
of a direct case than
我从没说过这个话题
I've never made before about this topic.
在这之前的大部分时间里我的基本外卖
Most of the time prior to this point,
my essential takeaway or
我给大家的基本信息是 == == = 可以在代码中共存
my essential message to people was,
== and === can coexist in your code,
你可以做出选择你不用躲过 ==
and you can make choices,
you don't have to avoid the ==,
我要对这一点提出更有力的论据。
I'm going to make a stronger
argument to this point.
您应该在所有可能的位置中选择 " == " 的更强的自变量。
The stronger argument that you should
prefer == in all possible places.
我知道这会让一些人震惊
And I know this gonna
shock a few people but
你必须要有开放的头脑来倾听这个论点
you're gonna have to have an open
mind to listen to this argument.
把我们讨论到的所有事情都放在一起
Taking everything in whole in totality
that we've talked about together,
包括我声称理解类型的代码是
including the fact that it is my claim
that code that understands types is
更好的代码不管选择如何
better code regardless of the choice.
在此范围内，我认为可以说 == = === 。
Within that context, I think I can make
the case that == is preferable to ===.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此了解类型总比不了解类型好。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So knowing the types
is always better than not knowing them.
密码的不确定性让代码难以理解
The uncertainty of code is
what make code hard to read,
它使代码易受虫子的影响。
it makes code susceptible to bugs.
有些人说不知道自己的类型的问题，我要
Some people respond to that problem of not
knowing their types by saying, I need to
更改我的编码样式以使用静态输入，如 TypeScript 和其他类型。
change my coding style to use static
typing, like TypeScript and the others.
我们要在一段时间里讨论 TypeScript
We're gonna talk about
TypeScript in just a moment but
我不认为这是解决这个问题的唯一对策。
I don't think that that is
the only response to this problem.
这个问题还有一个反应， >> Kyle Simpson:
There's another response to this problem,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
== 不是关于未知类型的比较，这不是它的对象，也不是
== is not about comparisons with unknown
type, that's not what it's for and that's
而不是你应该用的，这和大多数人的说法是相反的。
not what you should use it for, that is
the opposite of what most people claim.
大多数人声称他们在不知道类型的情况下使用 == ，然后
Most people claim that they use == when
they don't know the types, and then they
就会掉到这些虫子里我是说别在那个场景里用它
fall into these bugs and I'm saying
don't use it in that scenario at all.
当您不知道类型时，永远不要使用 == 。
Never use the == when you
don't know the types, ever.
仅当了解类型时才使用 == 。
Only use the == when you know the types.
就像我说的你应该努力了解你的
And as I said, you should strive
to know the types in your
尽可能的比较。
comparisons as much as possible.
它是关于与已知类型和 ( 可选) 的比较，
It's about comparisons with
known types and optionally,
如果你想强迫他
if you like to have coercions.
也许你的所有比较都知道这些类型和
Maybe all of your comparisons
you know the types and
也许所有这些类型都是平等的而且你从来没有使用过胁迫
maybe all of those types are always
equal and you never use coercion, and
仍在此场景中 == 是首选项。
still in that scenario == is preferable.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 但也许有些时候你想利用
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: But maybe some of
the times you wanna take advantage
而 == 是你唯一的选择
of coercion, and
then == is essentially your only option.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以让我们在这里挖掘细微的细节因为我知道你们中的一些人
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's dig into
the nuance here because I know some of you
我就不会相信我了好吗
are not gonna believe me just
right off the bat, okay?
如果你知道对比中的类型你就会发现
Let's dig into the nuance here,
if you know the types in a comparison,
我觉得你应该
and I think you should.
如果您知道比较中的类型，并且这两种类型都是相同的，
If you know the types in a comparison and
both of the types are the same,
那么我们已经知道 == = ===。
then we already know that
== is identical to ===.
我们已经知道他们的互换性，在你了解他们的情况下
We already know their interchangeable,
in the case where you know them and
他们是一样的
they are the same.
你是说，是的，但这并不意味着我不知道如何使用它。
So you're saying, yeah, but that doesn't
mean that I don't know how to use it.
我的索赔是，在该方案中不需要使用 ===
My claim is, using === is
unnecessary in that scenario and
你应该更喜欢短的 ==
you should prefer the shorter ==.
这不仅仅是用一个更少的字符，好吗 ?
That is not just about using
one fewer character, okay?
有些人知道 TypeScript 做了很多工作
Some of you know that
TypeScript does a lot of work,
即使你不做任何类型的人
even if you don’t do any types at all.
在这里我没有任何类型的注释
Here I have no types annotated once so
ever and
还做一大堆推论，推断，好吗 ?
it still does a bunch of inference,
type inference, okay?
在此特定情况下，错误告诉我的是我不应该使用 ===
In this particular case what the error
is telling me is I should not use a ===
因为类型不同，这将始终为 false。
because the types are different,
and this will always be false.
现在我不知道你的事了
Now I don't know about you, but
我认为这是一个特别有用的错误信息。
I find that to be a particularly
useful error message.
告诉我别做傻事总是会失败的
It is telling me don't do something
stupid that would always fail,
百分百保证会失败好吗
100%, guaranteed to fail, all right?
它知道它会失败，它告诉我不要无谓地这样做。
It knows that it'll fail, and
it tells me don't do it unnecessarily.
我的主张是如果我们认为合理
My claim is that if we
find to be reasonable,
那么反阳性也是合理的。
then the counter positive
is also reasonable.
如果在类型不匹配时使用它是毫无意义的，
If it is pointless to use it
when the types don't match,
当类型匹配时，不需要使用它。
it is unnecessary to use
it when the types do match.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果我们喜欢我们的人抱怨什么时候没有意义的话，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If we like for our linter
to complain when it'd be pointless,
那我们就应该有个在不必要的情况下抱怨的过客
then we ought to have a linter that
complains when it's unnecessary.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果你知道对比的类型，他们就不同了，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So if you know the types
in a comparison, and they're different,
这才是有趣的地方
this is where things get interesting,
因为用 === 是在保护你，救你。
because supposedly using the ===
is protecting you and saving you.
但是你知道类型，你知道不一样的，一个 ===
But if you know the types and you know
them to be different, a single === will
始终失败，这是我们刚刚讨论的 TypeScript 规则的全部原因。
always fail, which is the whole reason for
that TypeScript rule we just talked about.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 它肯定会被打破，你和我一起吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It would definitely
be broken, you're with me?
所以你只有两个选择如果你知道这些类型和
So your only two options in that case,
if you know the types and
他们不匹配你有两种选择
they don't match you,
have one of two options,
您可以不进行比较，也可以使用 ==。
you can either not do the comparison or
you can use ==.
那是你唯一的选择
Those are your only two options and
如果你知道对比的类型他们就不一样了
if you know the types in a comparison,
and they're different,
仅相当于单个 == 的值为两个或更多 ===。
the only equivalent to a single
== would be two or more ===.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你不能有 ===
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You
can not have a === and
如果类型不同，那么 == 是等效的，这是不可能的。
a == be equivalent when the types
are different, that is impossible.
因此，如果您有一个可以使用一个 == 的方案，或者您可以使用两个或多个
So if you have a scenario where you could
use one ==, or you could use two or
more === ，估计哪个要慢，两个 ===。
more ===, guess which one is
going to be slower, the two ===.
让 JavaScript 进行胁迫的速度更快
It is faster to let JavaScript
do the coercion than it is for
你要做些露体的
you to make a bunch of explicit ones.
如果你要做 3 个或者 3 个
And it gets even worse if
you have to do three or
四取决于胁迫的复杂性
four depending upon
the complexity of the coercion.
现在我说慢，用引号，因为我们说的是微秒。
Now I say slower, in air quotes because
we're talking about microseconds.
但在此场景中， === 绝对不可能。
But it is absolutely not possible for
a === to be faster in this scenario.
在最好的情况下，它是平等的，实际上，
In the best possible scenario,
it's equal and actually, in reality,
只是几次把它们列出来比较慢
it's just a tiny bit slower to
list them out multiple times.
现在我不是在说仅在表演上是个论点
Now I'm not making the case that on
performance alone that's an argument,
因为微秒差异不是相关的。
because the microsecond
difference is not that relevant.
但这就是 === 不高于 ==的大案的一部分。
But this is part of the larger case
that === is not somehow superior to ==.
很多人说 === 更快，不是强迫的。
Many people have said === is
faster cuz it doesn't coerce.
那是橘子和橘子的比较
That's a apples to oranges comparison,
cutz ，你说一个 === 快了一个 == ，不等于。
cuz you're saying one === is faster
than one == and they're not equivalent.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果你真的在看苹果，两个 ===
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you actually looked
at an apples to apples two === is always
有点慢于一个 ==
going to be a little
bit slower than one ==.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，如果您在此场景中，可以执行两个 === 或
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So if you're in this
scenario where you could do two === or
三，四，或者你可以做一个 ==，
three or four, or you could do one ==,
我说你应该更喜欢那两个是单一的 ==
I say you should prefer the faster
of the two which is the single ==,
这一论点的一部分，肯定不是整个论点的一部分。
part of the argument, certainly
not the entirety of the argument.
最后，如果类型不同，而两个或更多的是比较，
And finally, if the types are different,
and two or more are what the comparisons,
就是你要用的，就是两个或者两个以上的 ===，
that's what you would use,
is two or more of the ===,
我的说法是它让读者失去了不必要的信息
my claim is that it's distracting the
reader with unnecessary type information,
例如，在 null 未定义的情况下。
like in the null undefined case,
for example.
没有人发现你在分散读者的注意力
And the no one find case, you're
distracting the reader there is these two
不同的空值和奇怪的古怪的差异
different empty values and they sort
of have weird quirky differences.
在大多数情况下，读者不需要看到这种情况，
That's not necessary for
the reader to see in most cases,
在大多数情况下，通过显式列出和您拥有的内容来分散它们的注意力
in most cases you're distracting them
by listing explicitly and what you have
要用的是更恰当的抽象性的强迫它是用 " ==" 来清除的
to use is the more properly abstracted
coercion that it's cleaner with the ==.
记住这就是你知道的类型，对，
Now remember,
this is if you know the types, right,
我只是想说你知道这些类型
I'm only making these claims
if you know the types.
通过了解这些类型
And by know the types,
我的意思是，对代码的读者来说，这些类型的含义是显而易见的。
I mean that it is obvious to the reader
of the code what the types will be.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 那么，对不起，还有一个，摘要幻灯片，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So what about, sorry,
there's one more, the summary slide,
当然
of course.
如果您知道类型，那么在摘要中，无论类型是否匹配，
This is if you know the types, so in
summary, whether the types match or not,
当你知道这些类型的时候， == 是更明智的选择，好吗 ?
== is the more sensible choice
when you know the types, okay?
当您了解类型时， == 是更明智的选择，因此
When you know the types,
== is the more sensible choice, so
让我们看看对方，在那些你不知道类型的情况下。
let's look at the other side, in those
cases where you don't know the types.
如果您不知道类型，这意味着您不充分了解代码，
If you do not know the types, that means
you don't fully understand the code,
这可能是不必要的要求
that may be an unnecessary requirement.
不能保证 100% ，你一直都知道
It is not possible to guarantee 100%,
you always know
整个系统的类型，不合理，不合理。
the types in the entire system,
that's not reasonable and rational.
因此，我承认有时会有比较的时候，
So I recognize that there will be
times when comparisons happen, and
还有一些不确定性
there's some uncertainty.
我的主张是，这应该是一个稀有的，而不是现状。
My claim is that that should be
a rarity rather than the status quo.
但它的意思是，不管它是稀有的还是现状，
But what it does mean, whether it's
a rarity or the status quo, is that that
由于这种不确定性，部分代码更难理解。
part of the code is harder to understand
as a result of that uncertainty.
因此，不知道这些类型意味着您无法完全了解该代码。
So not knowing the types means that
you don't fully understand that code.
最佳响应是对其进行折射，以便您可以了解类型( 如果可能) 。
The best response is to refractor it so
that you can know the types, if possible.
如果你不知道这些类型
If you don't know the types, and
这种不明朗的因素必须得到处理
that uncertainty of knowing
just has to be dealt,
然后至少让读者明白这一点。
then at least make sure that
that is obvious to the reader.
请确保读者对此处存在某些不确定性是显而易见的。
Make sure that it is obvious to the reader
that there is some uncertainty here.
输入代码注释，
Put a code comment,
这样的话读者就不会有虚假的安全感，
structure it in such a way that the reader
doesn't have a false sense of security,
他们认为他们知道发生了什么，而且实际上是不确定的。
they think they know what's happening,
and actually it's uncertain.
应该是很明显，不管你怎么做都不确定
It should be super obvious that it's
uncertain in whatever possible way you
因为我们再次试图传达我们的意图
can, because again we're trying
to communicate our intent.
我的意思是告诉你这很不确定
My intent here is to tell you that
it's uncertain, just so you know,
就会有龙，对，这就是我们想用我们的代码来做的。
beware there'll be dragons, right,
that's what we wanna do with our code.
这对读者来说应该是显而易见的
So it should be obvious to the reader, and
您可以使用的最明显的信号是 ===。
the most obvious signal you can
use about that uncertainty is ===.
如果你遵循我在第一条条款中所主张的
If you followed what I argued
in the first set of clauses,
即，当您了解类型时， == 是首选项，然后使用
which is that the == is preferable when
you know the types, then the usage of
=== 应该为您不知道类型的情况保留。
=== should be reserved for
the cases where you don't know the types.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以它向读者发出信号，我不知道这些类型，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So that it signals to
the reader, I don't know the types,
我在努力保护自己
I'm trying to protect myself.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 它应该跳出来，读者应该看到，这里有一个 === 。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It should jump out,
the reader should see, there's a === here.
这意味着这些类型存在一些不确定性，并且
That means there are some
uncertainty of the types, and
我们得把自己限制在一个角落
we need to restrict ourselves so
we don't run into a corner case.
>> Kyle Simpson: 还有，我说不知道类型是等价的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Also, I would say that
not knowing the types is equivalent
以假定将发生类型转换或类型强制。
to assuming that type conversion or
type coercion will occur.
这相当于假设如果你不知道这些类型
It's equivalent to assuming that
because if you don't know the types,
最坏的情况是它们不匹配并且在某些情况下不匹配
the worst case scenario is that they will
not match and they will not match in some
一种奇怪的方式来引起一些奇怪的胁迫
weird way that invokes some
weird corner case of coercion.
你得想好最坏的情况
You need to assume the worst case.
所以不知道这种情况的类型与最坏的情况是一样的。
So not knowing the types of equivalent
to that worst case coercion.
唯一明智的回应是
And the only sensible response to that,
唯一安全的响应是使用 === 保护您自己。
the only safe response to that is
protect yourself from that with a ===.
如果你不能也不能，用一个你能知道的，
In summary if you can't or won't,
use a style where you can know and
有明显的类型，唯一明智的
have obvious types,
the only thing that is sensible and
== = 是合理的。
reasonable is for you to use the ===.
如果使用 ===，这不是针对您的攻击。
This isn't meant to be an attack
against you if use ===.
我只是想以实际行动来重新讨论
I'm just trying to reframe this
discussion in a way that actually moves
而不是一场宗教争论的讨论
the discussion forward rather than
a sort of religious debate of well,
这本书说从来没有用过，我也从来没有考虑过别的。
this one book said never use it, and
I've never even considered anything else.
我其实是想在这里做一套理性的分析
I'm actually trying to make a rational
set of analysis here to come to some real
结论不只是一个人说的好吗
conclusion, not just the thing
that one guy said, okay?
你可以测试我的分析，如果你不同意我的理由，那就好。
And you can test my analysis, if you don't
agree with my rationale, that's okay.
但我要搁置这件案子让你能测试理由
But I'm laying out this case so
that you can test the rationale.
即使在这种情况下我也会这样说
And I would say this,
even in that scenario,
你要用一个 === 的每个地方都是一样的，
where every place that you would
use a === would be the same,
就相当于一个 ==，所以你说，你知道，我们就是想简单的
it would be equivalent to a ==, and so you
say, you know, we just want the simpler
因为林德赫斯特说的，我们想用的东西到处都是 == = 。
thing we want to use === everywhere
because that's what Lyndhurst says.
你实际做的是把错误的语义信号发送给
What you are actually doing is sending
the wrong semantic signal to a reader of
你的密码
your code.
我在这些案子里保护自己因为我不知道
Which is I’m protecting myself in all of
these cases because I don't know about
类型。
the types.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 那不是传达你要传达的信息
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And that is not
communicating what you put to communicate
向未来的读者提供密码
to future readers of the code.
了解语义信号的代码的未来读者，
Future readers of the code
that see the semantic signal,
我不知道类型，所以我要回一些 === 保护自己，
I don't know about the types, so I've to
fall back to some === to protect myself,
这些代码的未来读者更有可能重写代码
those future readers of the code are much
more likely to rewrite the code,
因为他们不懂
because they don't understand it.
他们会第一次做你该做的
They're gonna do what you should
have done the first time.
他们会把它重构到已知类型的地方
They're gonna refactor it to
where the types are known.
不确定对于您的代码并不是一件好事。
Uncertainty is not a good thing for
your code basis.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，摘要中，使您的类型为已知和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So in summary,
making your types known and
就会有更好的密码
obvious just leads to better code.
没有任何理由可以提出相反的意见。
There's no argument that can
be made to the contrary.
了解类型可导致更好的代码，如果类型已知，那么 == 始终最好。
Knowing the types leads to better code and
if the types are known, == is always best.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 在每种情况下，最好是在已知类型的情况下 ==
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In every scenario ==
is best when the types are known and
在任何情况下都不能返回到 ===。
in any scenario where you can't
you should fall back to ===.
我很清楚这件案子很有争议
I'm fully aware that case
is quite controversial.
而你们中的任何一个人都不太相信
And it's unlikely that any of you
are convinced at the moment by that
讨论。
discussion.
但我真正想问的是，你要回去思考。
But what I would really like to ask
you is to go back and think about it.
后退并测试此原理，并针对您的代码进行测试。
Go back and test this rationale and
test it against your code.
问自己真的是写更清楚的代码吧
Ask yourself if you really are writing
better code that is more clearly
通过简单使用 === 来传达其意图。
communicating its intent by
simply using === everywhere.
我不能为你做这些决定
I can't make those decisions for you but
我认为我已经做了最有力的例子，因为我可以重新分析他们的原因。
I think I've made the most solid case that
I can, for why they should be re-analysed.